When Prime Minister Kamala Passat-Bissessa said the United States should kill alleged drug dealers violently,
no citizen was listed among the dead.
On the U.S.'s fifth airstrike, Trinidadians' Chad Joseph and another man identified only as Samaru
were among six people killed on Tuesday,
taking the number of alleged narco-traffickers killed by the U.S. since September 2nd to 27.
Joseph's grandfather, Cornel Clement, who denied his grandson was a drug trafficker,
says he has no choice but to trust in God.
Now he questions the U.S.'s method of dealing with the situation.
I watch out this and wickedness.
Because why are we killing people to run through?
They're not meant that yet, they're not supposed to be that way.
You say he will have a drug trafficker.
No, no, no. The boy has no drug trafficker.
He just make them run and come back.
Joseph's grandmother, Christine, says her grandson was in Venezuela for the past three months
and wanted desperately to return home, but his previous attempts failed.
The first time he was coming up, there was coming, they shoot up the boat.
He ended up surviving on some little beach.
And some people stick to him because I talked to him and I talked to him one of the ladies too.
And the second time I said he's coming, I get his mother two days ago after.
She told me he must come and something with the boat again.
So he go back.
A short distance away, residents of Los Pesos village...
What the U.S. do in there?
I think it's inhumane.
Right?
If only really...
All right.
Only blow the boat up.
What evidence it have showing really is drugs, you know, and stuff like that.
Let me say is guns.
Or even say is human trafficking, anything.
You can't...
Why is the closure the family having now?
Calls and messages to the Prime Minister and Defence Minister Wayne Sturge went unanswered.
Months ago, Sturge said during a post-Cabinet media briefing that any...
I need West...
When Prime Minister Kamala Passat-Bissessa said...